{"animation_end_text": "You're Internet Legends!", "animation_middle_text": "You're growing stronger...", "animation_start_text": "Wait. What's this?", "collection_id": "Quiz", "complete_screen_title_first_line": "Hooray!", "complete_screen_title_second_line": "You did it", "confirm_restart_button_text": "That's OK", "correct_selection_texts": ["Correct", "You got it!", "Spot on!", "Right answer", "That's right!", "Great work"], "customize_button_text": "Personalise your Legend", "document_id": "6560851627868160", "finished_button_text": "Finished", "incorrect_selection_texts": ["Have another go", "Not quite. Try again", "Oops, nearly got it", "Give it another try", "That's not quite right"], "locale": "root", "next_question_button_text": "Next question", "parents_guide_text": "Ready to discover more ways to stay safer online together?", "project_id": "published", "questions": [{"answer_one_text": "One year", "answer_three_text": "Forever", "answer_two_text": "Until I delete it", "correct_answer": "answer_three", "extra_info_body": "<p>Make sure you only post things you're comfortable with other people seeing.</p>", "extra_info_title": "Even if you delete your original post, the image could have been copied and shared by someone else.", "overlay_title": "Correct", "pillar": "be_sharp", "question_text": "How long could a photo you post on social media stay online for?", "title": "Question 1"}, {"answer_one_text": "Reply to it and tell the poster they're wrong", "answer_three_text": "Report it and talk to an adult if you feel upset or angry", "answer_two_text": "Ignore it completely", "correct_answer": "answer_three", "extra_info_body": "<p>The right people can help to remove it.</p>", "extra_info_title": "The best way to stop false information from being spread online is to report it when you see it.", "overlay_title": "Good work", "pillar": "be_sharp", "question_text": "You read something untrue about yourself in an online comment.", "title": "Question 2"}, {"answer_one_text": "My phone number", "answer_three_text": "My address", "answer_two_text": "My pet's name", "correct_answer": "answer_two", "extra_info_body": "<p>If you aren't sure, ask an adult before posting any personal details.</p>", "extra_info_title": "It's OK to share some things about yourself online, but not everything.", "overlay_title": "Excellent", "pillar": "be_sharp", "question_text": "Which piece of information is OK for you to share online?", "title": "Question 3"}, {"answer_one_text": "Share them immediately, no one will mind", "answer_three_text": "Share them, but only to a private group", "answer_two_text": "Ask the people in the pictures if you can share them", "correct_answer": "answer_two", "extra_info_body": "<p>Even if you think it's fine, they might not be OK with them showing up online.</p>", "extra_info_title": "It's important to get people's permission before you share any photos or videos they're in.", "overlay_title": "Well done", "pillar": "be_sharp", "question_text": "You've taken some pictures at a friend's party and want to share them online.", "title": "Question 4"}, {"answer_one_text": "Show a friend and ask how it makes them feel", "answer_three_text": "Stop watching and talk to an adult about what you've seen", "answer_two_text": "Keep watching \u2014 maybe it gets better", "correct_answer": "answer_three", "extra_info_body": "", "extra_info_title": "If anything you see online makes you feel strange, upset or uncomfortable, always make sure you speak to a grown up about it.", "overlay_title": "Nice job", "pillar": "be_sharp", "question_text": "You start watching a video that makes you feel really uncomfortable.", "title": "Question 5"}, {"answer_one_text": "Sounds funny. Let's watch!", "answer_three_text": "Share it with my friends without watching it", "answer_two_text": "Check to see who the message is from before clicking", "correct_answer": "answer_two", "extra_info_body": "<p>Take a moment to check where emails and messages are coming from and ask yourself if you trust the sender before forwarding anything on.</p>", "extra_info_title": "Sometimes hackers can tempt us with exciting headlines.", "overlay_title": "Fantastic", "pillar": "be_secure", "question_text": "You're sent a link to a video called 'Bet you can't watch this without laughing'.", "title": "Question 6"}, {"answer_one_text": "6 characters", "answer_three_text": "12 characters", "answer_two_text": "8 characters", "correct_answer": "answer_two", "extra_info_body": "<p>The longer the password the better &mdash; as long as you can remember it!</p>", "extra_info_title": "Strong passwords should be at least 8 characters long, with a mix of upper and lowercase letters, numbers, and symbols.", "overlay_title": "That's right", "pillar": "be_secure", "question_text": "Passwords should have at least this many characters in order to be strong and secure.", "title": "Question 7"}, {"answer_one_text": "A grown up I trust, like my mum or dad", "answer_three_text": "My teacher", "answer_two_text": "My best friend", "correct_answer": "answer_one", "extra_info_body": "", "extra_info_title": "It's important to keep your password as secret as possible, so don't share it with anyone you don't need to.", "overlay_title": "Correct", "pillar": "be_secure", "question_text": "It's OK to share my password with...", "title": "Question 8"}, {"answer_one_text": "Letters, numbers and symbols", "answer_three_text": "Letters, symbols and dates", "answer_two_text": "Numbers, letters and emoji", "correct_answer": "answer_one", "extra_info_body": "<p>It's best not to include any personal information, like your birthday.</p>", "extra_info_title": "It's important to have a variety of different letters, numbers and symbols in your password.", "overlay_title": "Good work", "pillar": "be_secure", "question_text": "What three things make up a strong password?", "title": "Question 9"}, {"answer_one_text": "Change your password immediately", "answer_three_text": "Delete the picture \u2014 maybe you just forgot", "answer_two_text": "Close your whole account", "correct_answer": "answer_one", "extra_info_body": "<p>The first step is always to change your password and make sure you aren't using the same one across important accounts.</p>", "extra_info_title": "Suspicious activity on any personal profile may mean you've been hacked.", "overlay_title": "Excellent", "pillar": "be_secure", "question_text": "You notice a picture was posted on your social media profile, but you didn't post it.", "title": "Question 10"}, {"answer_one_text": "A key", "answer_three_text": "A star", "answer_two_text": "A padlock", "correct_answer": "answer_two", "extra_info_body": "<p>Do this before entering your password, or any other information.</p>", "extra_info_title": "Make sure the website you're visiting is the real deal by checking that the URL starts with https:// and has a little green padlock to the left of it.", "overlay_title": "Well done", "pillar": "be_alert", "question_text": "Before sharing any information on a website, what symbol should you look for?", "title": "Question 11"}, {"answer_one_text": "Pharming", "answer_three_text": "Phaffing", "answer_two_text": "Phishing", "correct_answer": "answer_two", "extra_info_body": "<p>Always check who sent the message and, if you don't recognise the source, it's best to steer clear.</p>", "extra_info_title": "Phishers will try lots of different things to get you to reveal sensitive information.", "overlay_title": "Nice job", "pillar": "be_alert", "question_text": "What is it called when scammers try to get personal information from you?", "title": "Question 12"}, {"answer_one_text": "Tell them \u2013 a present will make your parents happy!", "answer_three_text": "Ask for their name and start a conversation", "answer_two_text": "Ask your parents if they know this person", "correct_answer": "answer_two", "extra_info_body": "", "extra_info_title": "Don't give away any details to someone you don't know, even if they're offering to give you something in return.", "overlay_title": "Fantastic", "pillar": "be_alert", "question_text": "Someone online says they know your parents and need your address to send them a gift.", "title": "Question 13"}, {"answer_one_text": "Send a fun selfie!", "answer_three_text": "Stop to think before sending anything", "answer_two_text": "Write a message back instead", "correct_answer": "answer_three", "extra_info_body": "<p>It can be tricky to tell real from fake. Stop to think and, if in doubt, ask an adult to help you check them out.</p>", "extra_info_title": "Sometimes people online aren't who they say they are.", "overlay_title": "That's right", "pillar": "be_alert", "question_text": "A celebrity you really like sends you a message saying they want a picture of you.", "title": "Question 14"}, {"answer_one_text": "Send it to a friend and ask them to download it", "answer_three_text": "Click it. It's free, so it should be fine", "answer_two_text": "Ask an adult if you can play before clicking anything", "correct_answer": "answer_two", "extra_info_body": "<p>Don't click on any suspicious links. They could lead to bad websites or put you at risk of being hacked.</p>", "extra_info_title": "Be wary of anything being given away for free online!", "overlay_title": "Correct", "pillar": "be_alert", "question_text": "You're sent a link to download a cool looking game for free.", "title": "Question 15"}, {"answer_one_text": "Tell the person, so they can read it for themselves", "answer_three_text": "Send your friend a private message saying you agree", "answer_two_text": "Tell your friend it's not OK and ask them to delete it", "correct_answer": "answer_two", "extra_info_body": "", "extra_info_title": "Always remember to treat others how you would like to be treated, online and off.", "overlay_title": "Good work", "pillar": "be_kind", "question_text": "A friend has posted something mean about someone you don't like.", "title": "Question 16"}, {"answer_one_text": "Nothing - I'll just try to ignore it", "answer_three_text": "Message them and ask them to stop", "answer_two_text": "Block the account", "correct_answer": "answer_two", "extra_info_body": "<p>Remember, you can report hurtful things you see online too.</p>", "extra_info_title": "Blocking helps you filter out any content you don't like, or that makes you feel uncomfortable.", "overlay_title": "Excellent", "pillar": "be_kind", "question_text": "You want to stop seeing posts from a person, or brand, online. How do you do it?", "title": "Question 17"}, {"answer_one_text": "Every time I see it happening", "answer_three_text": "Only if I know the bully", "answer_two_text": "Only when it involves me or my friends", "correct_answer": "answer_one", "extra_info_body": "<p>Be brave and speak up.</p>", "extra_info_title": "Bad behaviour should be called out every time. Even if things aren't hurtful to you, they could be to someone else.", "overlay_title": "Well done", "pillar": "be_kind", "question_text": "When should you report online bullying?", "title": "Question 18"}, {"answer_one_text": "Tripping", "answer_three_text": "Tracking", "answer_two_text": "Trolling", "correct_answer": "answer_two", "extra_info_body": "<p>Don't get involved in arguments and remember to report trolls when you see them.</p>", "extra_info_title": "The internet should be used to spread positivity, not to make people upset.", "overlay_title": "Nice job", "pillar": "be_kind", "question_text": "What do we call it when people try to start fights, or make others angry on purpose, online?", "title": "Question 19"}, {"answer_one_text": "Ask an adult if the word is OK", "answer_three_text": "Search for the word to find out what it means", "answer_two_text": "Share it. It's already online so it probably won't hurt anyone", "correct_answer": "answer_one", "extra_info_body": "<p>It's a great chance to learn something new!</p>", "extra_info_title": "It's always better to ask someone about the things you don't understand.", "overlay_title": "That's right", "pillar": "be_kind", "question_text": "You want to share a funny meme you found, but there's a word in it you don't understand.", "title": "Question 20"}], "reject_restart_button_text": "Go back", "repo_id": "gweb-internet-legends-quiz", "resource_button_text": "Explore Parents Page", "restart_screen_subtitle": "All your progress and personalisation will be lost.", "restart_screen_title": "Restart challenge", "share_button_text": "Share", "site_id": "gweb-internet-legends-quiz", "workspace_id": null}